Guide to James R. Hoffa Documentation collection, 1954-1976 LAC0005
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Trial Documentation, 1962-1966; Series 7
  - US vs. Hoffa, Court of Appeals, 1965-1966; Series 7 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    U.S. vs. Hoffa in the United States Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit, Sept. 1965/April 1966
  - US vs. Hoffa, Court of Appeals, 1966; Series 7 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    U.S. vs. Hoffa in the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit (nos. 14892-14898), May 10, 1966
  - US vs. Hoffa, Court of Appeals 7th Circuit, 1964-1966; Series 7 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    U.S. vs. Hoffa in the U.S. Court of Appeals for the Seventh Circuit (no. 14892), Appeal from the U.S. District Court for the Northern District of Illinois, n.d.
  - Zagri at DRIVE Seminar, 1964; Series 7 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Mr. Zagri on Chattanooga Trial, Transcript of Wisconsin DRIVE Seminar, March 30/31-April 1, 1964, photocopy of transcript from Sound Studio [includes handwritten notes].
- Subject files, 1960-1966; Series 8
  This series contains background materials on issues of relevance for the IBT and James R. Hoffa: an analysis of the Teamster monitorship in the Federal Bar Journal, and materials on highway safety in the context of the debate about the National Highway Safety Act.
  - Teamster Monitorship, 1960; Series 8 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Article by L.B. Mandelbaum on "The Teamster Monitorship," Federal Bar Journal 20:2 (Spring 1960).
  - Murder by Motor, 1966; Series 8 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    "Murder by Motor," Study by the American Trial Lawyers Association, Jan. 1966
  - IBT Letters To Affiliate, 1960; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1961-1971; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - JRH - Re Contracts And Agreements, 1962, 1966; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Letters From President William Loeb To justices, 1966; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - JRH Local 299 Election eaflets, 1968; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - JRH - Re Frank Fitzsimmons As Acting President, President Resolutions, 1971; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Banking and Security, 1971; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Edward Partin, 1971; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - JRH - Memorial Service, 30 July 1995; Series 8 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Re-printed and photocopied materials, 1962-1965; Series 9
  This series contains a collection of re-printed, and photocopied materials about James R. Hoffa. These materials cover the time period 1962-1965.
  - Ralph and Estelle James, 1965; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Ralph and Estelle James [1965]
  - Conversation on Revolution, 1962; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Excerpt from "A Conversation on Revolution" by Scott Buchanan, photocopy [1962?]
  - Hoffa's Impact on Teamster Wages, 1964; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Ralph and Estelle James, "Hoffa's Impact on Teamster Wages," Institute of Industrial Relations, reprint 247, Berkeley, CA, 1964.
  - Jim Clay, Hoffa, 1965; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Jim Clay, Hoffa! Ten Angels Swearing, Beaverdam, VA" Beaverdam Press, 1965 (unbound book copy).
  - Hoffa's Acquisition of Industrial Power, 1963; Series 9 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Ralph and Estelle James, Hoffa's Acquisition of Industrial Power, Institute of Industrial Relations, reprint 202, Berkeley, CA, 1963.
- Unpublished materials, 1964-1965; Series 10
  This series contains unpublished materials about James R. Hoffa.
  - S. Castor, report, 1964; Series 10 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Sharon Castor, James Hoffa (unpublished report with letter), July 14, 1964.
  - James Clay, 1965; Series 10 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    James Clay, Ten Angels Swearing: The True Story of James R. Hoffa, unpublished manuscript, no date [publication in 1965].
  - James Hoffa Memorial Service, July 30, 1995; Series 10 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - James Hoffa Photographs, undated; Series 10 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Picture of Dinner for Mr. Joyce, 1979; LAC0005 Series 10 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Picture of Josephine Poszywak Hoffa and Barbara Hoffa holding Child meeting Santa Claus, LAC0005 (Box SHARED Box 31, Folder 18)
- James R. Hoffa Memorial Scholarship Fund, 2002-2011; Series 11; 1 Linear Feet 1 flat box
  This series consists of literature regarding the James R. hoffa Memeorial Scholarship Fund. Subjects include events and supporters. Items are dated between 2002 and 2011
  Items are organized by date.
  - 2nd Annual invitational Golf Tournament, 2 May - 4 May, 2002; Series 11 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - 7th Annual invitational Golf Tournament, 3rd annual Texas Hold 'Em poker Tournament, 19 May - 21 May, 2008; Series 11 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - We thank you for your support of the 2011 James R. Hoffa Memorial Scholarship Fund, Series 11 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Platinum Sponsors, "Looking to the Future", 16 March, 2011; Series 11 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The James R. Hoffa Memorial Scholarship Fund Dinner, 16 March, 2011; Series 11 (Box 11, Folder 5)